Contact

9064583098 (Home) samriddhabasu1234@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/samriddhabasu-cloud (LinkedIn) samriddha.is-a.dev/ (Portfolio)

Top Skills

<u>Ja</u>va

Object-Oriented Programming (OOP)

C (Programming Language)

Languages

English (Full Professional)
Bengali (Native or Bilingual)
Hindi (Full Professional)
French (Limited Working)

Certifications

Advanced C Programming: Pointers

Learn to Earn Cloud Security

Challenge: Level 3

Learn to Earn Cloud Security

Challenge: Level 1

Learn to Earn Cloud Security

Challenge: Level 2

Exploring Data with Looker

Samriddha Basu

1x Microsoft Certified: Azure Fundamentals || Technical Head at Computer Society of India (CSI) - SRM NCR || PR HEAD at GFG SRM NCR Chapter

New Delhi

Summary

A sophomore pursuing B.Tech in CSE with specialisation in Cloud Computing at SRM IST Delhi-NCR Campus. I'm an ardent technophile and a cloud enthusiast, I love connecting with people and having a network of like-minded people. I'm pretty well at presenting and speaking in public. I have a good command on C/C++(5-star in HackerRank), Java and trying my hands on Android Development using Kotlin. I stick to a task until it gets done perfectly. Recently I have successfully completed the requirements to be recognised as a Microsoft Certified: Azure Fundamentals. I currently am the Technical Head at CSI SRM NCR Chapter and PR Head at GFG SRM NCR Chapter. Public Relations and Tech have been my domain since my freshman days and hope to explore other domains too. I am a quick learner and can adapt to changes real guick. My short term goal as of now is to master Android Development and complete my Google Digital Leader and AWS Cloud Practitioner(CLF-C01)certifications. I'm a team player and can lead a team from front. I believe in wise work and staying loyal to the organisation I'm in.

Experience

Computer Society of India (CSI) - SRM NCR 1 year 4 months

Technical Head February 2022 - Present (4 months)

Ghaziabad, Uttar Pradesh, India

P.R. junior Lead April 2021 - February 2022 (11 months) Modinagar, Uttar Pradesh, India

A lovely experience, meeting new people (although virtually), making new connections, gathering knowledge from every nook and corner; all in all would

never regret my days with this post. Also would extend my gratitude towards my seniors, who counted on me and I hope I had not let them down.

Core Member of Students Council February 2021 - February 2022 (1 year 1 month) India

When we work in a team, we actually get to know the value of unity, leadership, and

tolerance, here in the core team of CSI SRM NCR Students' Chapter, I have been personally gaining a lot of knowledge, also have been imparting wherever and whenever I got a chance to, and I can confidently state that, yes! I have been contributing being in a community.

GeeksforGeeks
Public Relations Officer
December 2021 - Present (6 months)
Ghaziabad, Uttar Pradesh, India

PrepBytes
Campus Business Manager
December 2021 - February 2022 (3 months)
Ghaziabad, Uttar Pradesh, India

Learned a lot in this three months

Education

SRM University (Sri Ramaswamy Memorial University)
Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Science & Engineering
· (September 2020 - September 2024)

St. Paul's Academy, Burdwan
High School Diploma · (April 2009 - March 2020)